what people don't understand is that these shows are an office yeah you know these shows we're
we're getting to we're getting to tell stories we're getting to play characters we are getting
to you know bring people into an imaginary world that's not theirs and that it's that is a craft
and it's an art and it's a great experience but at the end of the day literally at the end of the
day like we sign a time card and we go home and it's an office like you're with co-workers
and sometimes that is a beautifully just um matched experience and sometimes it has more texture
it's a good word I like that you know sometimes it has more texture and I think we're also in a
in a business of big personalities we're in a business of big goals and intentions and that
makes for a different type of dynamic than like oh we work at a restaurant
very much on the upper east side of New York